### Personal Info

- □ saba.marzoughi18@gmail.com
- م <u>LinkedIn</u>
- % GitHub
- (\$ Iran Tehran

# Fatemeh (Saba) Marzoughi

Front-end Developer
React & React Native

#### About me

I'm a Software Engineer with a passion for Frontend. I have been practicing for 5 years now, and I believe I'm ready for my next challenge where I can develop beautiful mobile applications and contribute to creation of a great software engineering team.

## Skills

- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript,
   TypeScript
- React
- React Native (Android, iOS)
- Electron (Windows, Mac OS)
- Rest API, GraphQL
- Redux, Context
- Native-Base, MUI
- Jest
- Realm, Hive
- Functional programming, OOP
- Strapi CMS, TestFlight
- Postman, Jira, Figma, Agile/Scrum team, Git

#### Education

(Sep 2017- Dec 2021)

Diploma: Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Software)

University: Islamic Azad University, Tehran-Central branch

## Work Experiences

<u>UniPlato</u>: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Australia (Remote), Aug 2022 – May 2023, <u>Visit Project</u>

- Brought the "Coffee" platform to its next level by building its desktop Mac Application using Electron and released over 20 versions of the app to TestFlight.
- Improved code base by building over 15 pixel-perfect, responsive, and clean **React** components which could be used by other team members in all the modules as our design system.
- Brought over 20 new features with demos to the platform by communicating with team members and using REST API, web sockets, and working with both functional and classbased components using React Library.
- Improved the stability of the platform by reviewing new team members' codes.
- Upgraded the platform by refactoring the old code structures of 2 old modules and bringing them back to the project.
- Comfortel: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Russia (Remote), Dec 2021 – May 2022, Visit Project

- Increased the usability of the "Techpal" platform by releasing its desktop app on 3 operating systems (Windows, Mac, and Linux) using Electron and its Android app using React-Native.
- Enhanced the team communication by customizing Mattermost platform both for desktop (Windows, Mac, and Linux) and mobile apps (Android).
- o Had experience using Flutter.
- Open Source and Freelancing: Front-End Developer
   Tehran (Remote), Apr 2020 Dec 2021, Visit Project
  - "MyPlayer" is an open-source React Native project using TypeScript, available on both iOS and Android which is a Video and Audio player with over 20 features on it.
  - Improved the portfolio of Bytino startup team by working on 2 open-source projects and linking them to the team webpage.